Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

Highest Degree: MS/M.Sc(Science) [INFORMATION

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

TECHNOLOGY]

KARTHIK P.V.N.S () Featured

Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Development, Design Development, Requirement Gathering, Data Structures, Root Cause Analysis, Data Classification, JSP Servlets, Angularis, Javascript, Ajax, jQuery, MySQL



Current Designation: Software Engineer

Current Company: PegaSystems

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad

Pref. Location: Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Development, Design Development, Requirement Gathering, Data Structures, Root Cause Analysis, Data Classification, JSP Servlets,

Angularjs, Javascript, Ajax, jQuery, MySQL

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

Agile Developer having 3.6+ years of experience in Information Technology.

My Core areas of skills are Design and Development using Java, Python, Angular, Spring, JavaScript, jQuery, MySQL & Hibernate.

Worked on development projects based on Angular, Spring, JavaScript & Hibernate Frameworks.

Worked on Pega Platform with the help of Data Pages and Report Definition.

Quick learner with good analytical, interpersonal and communication skills.

Very quick in identifying the root cause for the application issues and delivering the fixes.

Willingness to learn, sincere towards commitments, hardworking.

Very helpful to the team in Knowledge sharing and making them comfortable with the application.

Ability to meet and exceed personal, business goals and objectives.

Work Experience

PegaSystems as Software Engineer Nov 2019 to Till Date

ADP as Member Tecnical May 2019 to Nov 2019

TCS as System Engineer Feb 2017 to May 2019

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (ECE) from gitam university in 2014

PG: MS/M.Sc(Science) (INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY) from International Institute of Information Technology in 2016

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
JSP, Servlets, HTML, AngularJs			
Java script, AJAX, JQuery			
RESTful, Spring, Hibernate			
Eclipse & RStudio			
Tortoise SVN, Oracle, MySQL			
Java,Python,C,R, Tomcat			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time